<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE book PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DocBook XML V4.5//EN" "http://www.oasis-open.org/docbook/xml/4.5/docbookx.dtd">
<?altova_sps http://www.altova.com/sps/Template/Publishing/docbook.sps?>
<book>
	<title>ngEO Web Client User Manual</title>
	<chapter>
		<title>Overview</title>
		<sect1>
			<title>What is ngEO ?</title>
			<para>NGEO is the Next Generation Earth Observation system designed to manage end-user Earth Observation services.</para>
		</sect1>
		<sect1>
			<title>Document Purpose</title>
			<para>This user guide provides a description of ngEO User Client interface and how to use it.</para>
		</sect1>
		<sect1>
			<title>
				ngEO Main Concepts
			</title>
			<variablelist>
			<varlistentry>
				<term>
					Dataset
				</term>
			<listitem>
					<para> A dataset is a group of products. Various criteria are used to define a dataset such as : the use of products in a particular domain, the products meta data attributes, the user community. </para>
					<para> There are four types of datasets: </para>
					<itemizedlist>
						<listitem><para>Native Dataset: products are grouped by the same mission/sensor/sensor mode/product type, it is basically an eoli like collection.</para>						</listitem>
						<listitem><para>Logical Dataset: is a dataset handled by the ngeo system for which products are associated.</para></listitem>						
						<listitem><para>Remote Dataset: is a  dataset handled by external catalogues either by another ngeo instances or by HMA catalogues. Like HMA datasets and GCM.</para>						</listitem>	
						<listitem><para>Virtual Dataset: it is a dataset composed by one of the above three type.</para></listitem>	
					</itemizedlist>
			</listitem>
			</varlistentry>		
			<varlistentry>
				<term>
					Product
				</term>
				<listitem>
				<para> There are four types of products supported by ngEO: </para>
					<itemizedlist>
						<listitem>
							<para>Archived Products :</para>
							<para>An archived product is a downloadable unit of Earth Observation data acquired during a given period, 
							having a given footprint (except in the case of global products) and processed to a certain level (i.e. Level 0, 1, 2, 3 or n).
							An archived product has always a product URI.
							</para>	
						</listitem>	
						<listitem>
							<para>Acquired Products :</para>
							<para>Acquired products are similar, in ngEO, to archived products except that product URL is not provided.
							Thus acquired products cannot be downloaded. Acquired products are only expected to be used in CDS datasets.
							</para> 
						</listitem>	
						<listitem>
							<para>Planned Products:</para>
							<para>Planned products are products that are not already acquired (i.e. their acquisition time is normally in the future) 
							but whose acquisition that can be nonetheless predicted.
							</para> 
						</listitem>	
						<listitem>
							<para>Cancelled  Products:</para>
							<para>They are former planned products that were removed from the planning. They are handled exactly as planned products and are only expected to be used in CDS datasets.</para>
						</listitem>	
					</itemizedlist>
			</listitem>
			</varlistentry>
			<varlistentry><term>Download Manager</term>
				<listitem><para>It is software which is retrieved and run in standalone. It is used to the download of product data.</para></listitem>	
			</varlistentry>
			
			<varlistentry><term>Directly downloadable product</term>
				<listitem><para>It is a product having a url which starts with http or https.</para></listitem>	
			</varlistentry>
			
			<varlistentry><term>Simple Data Access Request</term>
				<listitem><para>It is a request issued from the user client in order to retrieve products having a url.</para></listitem>	
			</varlistentry>
			<varlistentry><term>Standing Order Data Access Request</term>
				<listitem><para>It is a request issued from the user client in order to schedule searches either by data or by time.</para></listitem>	
			</varlistentry>
			</variablelist>
		</sect1>
	<sect1>
		<title>How to read this guide?</title>
		<itemizedlist>
			<listitem><para><xref linkend="gettingstarted"/>: It is a chapter to summarize the main procedures to start dealing with the application functionalities.</para></listitem>
			<listitem><para><xref linkend="das"/>: It is a chapter to describe the functionalities and widgets of Data Services Area Menu.</para></listitem>
			<listitem><para><xref linkend="account"/>: It is a chapter to describe the functionalities and widgets of My account Menu.</para></listitem>
		</itemizedlist>
	</sect1>
	</chapter>
		
	<chapter id="gettingstarted">
		<title>Getting Started</title>
		<sect1 id="howtosearch">
			<title>How to make a Catalog Search?</title>
			<itemizedlist>
				<listitem><para>Launch the application and click on "Data Services Area" link :
					<graphic fileref="screenshots/homePage.jpg"/>
				</para></listitem>
				<listitem><para>Click on the Datasets icon on the tool bar <inlinegraphic fileref="screenshots/toolBarIcons/datasetsIcon.jpg"/>, the Dataset Selection widget is then opened.
					<graphic fileref="screenshots/datasetSelectionWidget.jpg"/>
				</para></listitem>
				<listitem><para>Click on one of the datasets.</para></listitem>
				<listitem><para>Click on the Search button below the datasets.</para></listitem>
				<listitem><para>The results are displayed on the map, and the status bar is updated.
					<graphic fileref="screenshots/statusBar.jpg"/>
				</para></listitem>
			</itemizedlist>
		</sect1>
		<sect1>
			<title>How to Download Products?</title>
			<itemizedlist>
				<listitem><para>Make a catalog search See <xref linkend="howtosearch"/>.</para></listitem>
				<listitem><para>Once the products are retrieved, click on Table button. Check the product id column in the results table:
				if the product is underlined, this means that the product can be downloaded unless it not downloadable.
				<graphic fileref="screenshots/downloadableProduct.jpg" />
				</para>
				<para>For a directly downloadable product, click on the product id, the direct download widget is opened.</para>
				<graphic fileref="screenshots/directDownloadWidget.jpg" />
				<para>According to the product url and to the download managers registered, the user can have the choice to either choose a download via:
					<itemizedlist>
						<listitem><para>the browser</para></listitem>
						<listitem><para>or the local download manager.</para></listitem>
					</itemizedlist>
				</para></listitem>
				<listitem><para>Click on "Via Browser" button to start the download.</para></listitem>
			</itemizedlist>
		</sect1>
		<sect1 id="simpleDARHowTo">
			<title>How to submit a Data Access request?</title>
			<itemizedlist>
				<listitem><para>Make a catalogue search See <xref linkend="howtosearch"/>.</para></listitem>
				<listitem><para>Once the products are retrieved, check the products to include in a Data Access Request.
				If the Retrieve Product button <inlinegraphic fileref="screenshots/retrieveProductButton.jpg" alt='RETRIEVE PRODUCT BUTTON'/> is still disabled this means that the products selected does not have a url.
				</para></listitem>
				<listitem><para>Click on Retrieve Product button, the data access widget is opened displaying the list of available download managers.
					<graphic fileref="screenshots/darWidget.jpg"/> 
				</para></listitem>
				<listitem><para>Click on Validate button. The request is validated and the server response is displayed underneath the button.
				If the request is successfully validated, the estimated size of the products are displayed and a notification message confirms that the
				request has been acknowledged. The Validation button is renamed into 'Confirm Your Request'
				If the validation has failed an error message is displayed with the list of available download managers.
					<graphic fileref="screenshots/validatedDARWidget.jpg"/> 
				</para></listitem>
				<listitem><para>Click on Confirm button. The request is confirmed and the server response is displayed underneath the button.
				If the request has been successfully confirmed, the request is being processed, unless an error message is displayed.
				</para></listitem>
			</itemizedlist>
			<!--p>When a user performs a search, he retrievs the products metadata. If the product has a url, it can be downloded<p-->
		</sect1>
		<sect1 id="STOHowTo">
			<title>How to submit a Standing Order?</title>
			<itemizedlist>
				<listitem><para>Launch the application and click on "Data Services Area" link.</para></listitem>
				<listitem><para>Click on the Datasets icon on the left tool bar.
					<inlinegraphic fileref="screenshots/toolBarIcons/datasetsIcon.jpg"/>, the Dataset Selection widget is opened.
				</para></listitem>
				<listitem><para>Click on one of the datasets in the dataset selection widget:
					<graphic fileref="screenshots/datasetSelectionWidget.jpg"/>
					The dataset is selected.
					</para></listitem>
				<listitem><para>Click on the Subscribe button on the left tool bar.
					<inlinegraphic fileref="screenshots/toolBarIcons/subscribeIcon.jpg"/>, the Subscribe widget is opened.
					<graphic fileref="screenshots/subscribeWidget.jpg"/>
					</para></listitem>
				<listitem><para>Fill in the Subscribe criteria and then click on the Order button, the Data Access Request widget is spawned-up.
					<graphic fileref="screenshots/darWidget.jpg"/>
				</para></listitem>
				<listitem><para>Click on Validate and then Submit to register the standing order.</para></listitem>
				
			</itemizedlist>
			<!--p>When a user performs a search, he retrievs the products metadata. If the product has a url, it can be downloded<p-->
		</sect1>
		<sect1 id="mapModeHowTo"><title>How to change Map Mode?</title>
			<para>Click on the 2D/3D <inlinegraphic fileref="screenshots/toolBarIcons/mapMode.jpg"/> button on the toolbar to change the map mode
				from 2D to 3D and inversely.</para>
		</sect1>
		
		<sect1 id="mapNavigationHowTo"><title>How to navigate on the Map?</title>
			<itemizedlist>
				<listitem><para> In order to zoom in either:
					<itemizedlist>
						<listitem><para>Click on the Zooum In <inlinegraphic fileref="screenshots/toolBarIcons/zoomInIcon.jpg"/>button on the toolbar</para></listitem> 
						<listitem><para>or move the mouse wheel in.</para></listitem> 
					</itemizedlist>
				</para></listitem>
				<listitem><para> In order to zoom out either:
					<itemizedlist>
						<listitem><para>Click on the Zooum Out <inlinegraphic fileref="screenshots/toolBarIcons/zoomOutIcon.jpg"/>button on the toolbar to zoom out.</para></listitem> 
						<listitem><para>or move the mouse wheel out.</para></listitem>
					</itemizedlist>
				</para></listitem>
				<listitem><para>Click on the Start View <inlinegraphic fileref="screenshots/toolBarIcons/startViewIcon.jpg"/>button on the toolbar to return back to the initial view</para></listitem>
			</itemizedlist>
		</sect1>
		
		<sect1 id="productsOnMapHowTo"><title>How to use products on the Map?</title>
			<itemizedlist>
				<listitem><para>Make a catalogue search See <xref linkend="howtosearch"/>.</para></listitem>
				<listitem><para>Once the products are retrieved, the related footprints are drawn on the map.</para></listitem>
				<listitem><para>Click inside a footprint:
					<itemizedlist>
						<listitem><para>the browse image is projected on the footprint,</para></listitem>
						<listitem><para>the product row is checked on the results table</para></listitem>
						<listitem><para>a popup widget is displayed with information on the selected product</para></listitem>
						<listitem><para>the icon <inlinegraphic fileref="screenshots/darIcon.jpg" alt='SIMPLE DAR icon'/> allows submitting a Simple Data access Request.
						Follow the same steps as in section <xref linkend="simpleDARHowTo"/>.
						<inlinegraphic fileref="screenshots/itemOnMap.jpg" alt='ITEM ON MAP'/>
						</para></listitem>						
					</itemizedlist>
				</para></listitem>
			</itemizedlist>
		</sect1>
		
		<sect1 id="layersHowTo"><title>How to select Layers?</title>
			<itemizedlist>
				<listitem><para>Click on the layers icon on the toolbar <inlinegraphic fileref="screenshots/toolBarIcons/layersIcon.jpg" alt='LAYERS ICON'/>.</para></listitem>		
				<listitem><para>The layers widget is displayed.
				<graphic fileref="screenshots/layersWidget.jpg" alt='LAYERS WIDGET'/>
				The Results Footprints layers is checked by default. It is the layer which displayed the result items footprints on the map.
				</para></listitem>		
				<listitem><para>Check the checkbox in front of the layer name, the layer is mapped on the map.
					<graphic fileref="screenshots/projectedLayers.jpg" alt='PROJECTED LAYERS'/>
				</para></listitem>	
				<listitem><para>In order to remove a layer from the map, uncheck the checkbox in front of the layer name.</para></listitem>
			</itemizedlist>
		</sect1>

		<sect1 id="backgroundsHowTo"><title>How to change Map Background?</title>
			<itemizedlist>
				<listitem><para>Click on the background icon on the toolbar <inlinegraphic fileref="screenshots/toolBarIcons/backgroundIcon.jpg" alt='BACKGROUND ICON'/>.</para></listitem>
				<listitem><para>The backgrounds' widget is displayed.
				 <graphic fileref="screenshots/backgroundsWidget.jpg" alt='BACKGROUND WIDGET'/>
				</para></listitem>
				<listitem><para>Click on the radio button in front of the background name to change the map background.</para></listitem>
			</itemizedlist>
		</sect1>
		
		<sect1 id="downloadManagersHowTo"><title>How to manage Download Managers?</title>
			<itemizedlist>
				<listitem><para>Click on My account on the menu bar.
					<inlinegraphic fileref="screenshots/menuBar.jpg" alt='MENUBAR IMAGE'/>
					The download managers already registered are displayed with the information details on each one of them.
					<graphic fileref="screenshots/downloadManagersView.jpg" alt='DOWNLOAD MANAGERS'/>
				</para></listitem>
				<listitem><para>If there is no download manager, click on Install Download Manager to install a new one.</para></listitem>
				<listitem><para>Select the row of the download manager to monitor, then, the command buttons statuses are updated 
					according to the download manager status.
					<graphic fileref="screenshots/downloadManagerCommands.jpg" alt='DOWNLOAD MANAGERS COMMANDS'/>
					<para><emphasis>A STOPPED download manager cannot no more be monitored, so the command buttons are disabled.</emphasis>
					<inlinegraphic fileref="screenshots/stoppedDM.jpg" alt='STOPPED DOWNLOAD MANAGER'/></para>
				</para></listitem>
				<listitem><para>Click on the Stop button <inlinegraphic fileref="screenshots/dmStopButton.jpg" alt='DOWNLOAD MANAGER STOP BUTTON'/>
					The Stop an ACTIVE or an INACTIVE download manager. 
				</para></listitem>
				<listitem><para>Click on the Stop Immediately button <inlinegraphic fileref="screenshots/dmStopImmediatelyButton.jpg" alt='DOWNLOAD MANAGER STOP IMMEDIATELY BUTTON'/>
					to stop definitively an ACTIVE or an INACTIVE download manager. 
					<para><emphasis>Please note that once the Stop or the Stop Immediately buttons are clicked, a new command cannot be issued from the user interface.
					A notification message is displayed to notify the user.</emphasis></para>
					<graphic fileref="screenshots/dmMonitoringMessage.jpg" alt='DOWNLOAD MANAGER MONITORING MESSAGE'/>
				</para></listitem>
			</itemizedlist>
		</sect1>
		
		<sect1 id="darsHowTo"><title>How to manage Data Access Requests?</title>
			<itemizedlist>
				<listitem><para>Click on My account on the menu bar.
					<inlinegraphic fileref="screenshots/menuBar.jpg" alt='MENUBAR IMAGE'/>
				</para></listitem>
				<listitem><para>Click Data Access Requests tab. On the left side, the download managers already assigned to data access requests
					are displayed. On the right side is displayed the list of the users' data access requests.
					<graphic fileref="screenshots/darsView.jpg" alt='DARS VIEW'/>
				</para></listitem>
				<listitem><para>Click on the first download manager name: only the data access requests assigned to the clicked download manager are displayed .
					<graphic fileref="screenshots/darsFiltering.jpg" alt='DARS FILTERING'/>
				</para></listitem>
				<listitem><para>Click on the second download manager name: only the data access requests assigned to the clicked download manager are displayed .
					<graphic fileref="screenshots/darsFiltering2.jpg" alt='DARS FILTERING 2'/>
				</para></listitem>
				<listitem><para>Click on the highlighted download manager name to disable the filtering.</para></listitem>
				<listitem><para>Click on the a data access request to expand it.
					<inlinegraphic fileref="screenshots/expandedDAR.jpg" alt='EXPANDED DAR'/>
					<para>The data access request id, status, completion percentage and the number of products are displayed.</para>
					<para>Buttons Pause, Resume and Stop Immediately buttons are displayed according to the request status.</para>
				</para></listitem>
				<listitem><para>Click on the Products button to visualize the products details.
					<graphic fileref="screenshots/expandedDARProducts.jpg" alt='EXPANDED DAR PRODUCTS'/>
				</para></listitem>
				<listitem><para>Click on the Stop definitively button <inlinegraphic fileref="screenshots/stopDefinitivelyButton.jpg" alt='DOWNLOAD MANAGER STOP DEFINITIVELY BUTTON'/>
					to cancel a processing or a paused data access request. 
				</para></listitem>
				<listitem><para>Click on the Pause button <inlinegraphic fileref="screenshots/pauseButton.jpg" alt='PAUSE BUTTON'/>
					to pause a processing data access request. 
				</para></listitem>
				<listitem><para>Click on the Resume button <inlinegraphic fileref="screenshots/resumeButton.jpg" alt='RESUME BUTTON'/>
					to change the status of a paused data access request to processing. 
				</para></listitem>
			</itemizedlist>
		</sect1>

	</chapter>
	
	<chapter id="das">
		<title>Data Access Services</title>
		<para>The data access services are the main functionalities of ngeo.
			They consist in :
		<itemizedlist>
			<listitem><para>catalogue searching using dataset geo-temporal criteria
				and/or dataset inherent criteria</para></listitem>
			<listitem><para>retrieving products metadata and data</para></listitem>
			<listitem><para>submitting data access requests</para></listitem>
			<listitem><para>visualizing and manipulating data on the map.</para></listitem>
		</itemizedlist>
		</para>
		<sect1>
			<title>Catalogue Search</title>
			<sect2><title>Datasets Selection</title>
				<para>
					The first and necessary step to make a catalogue search is to
					choose a dataset. The dataset selection widget is accessible by clicking on
					the <inlinegraphic fileref="screenshots/toolBarIcons/datasetsIcon.jpg" /> button.
					When the button is clicked, the widget is opened and it displays
					the list of available datasets. Each dataset is represented by
					its name and the number of items it contains.
					<graphic fileref="screenshots/datasetSelectionWidget.jpg" />
				</para>
				<para>
					<inlinegraphic fileref="screenshots/tip.jpg" /> Only datasets with search authorization are displayed.
				</para>
				<para>
					<inlinegraphic fileref="screenshots/tip.jpg" /> The icon <inlinegraphic fileref="screenshots/viewDisabled.jpg" /> means that you cannot view the dataset products, i.e. browse the product image in the map.
				</para>
				<para>
					<inlinegraphic fileref="screenshots/tip.jpg" /> The icon <inlinegraphic fileref="screenshots/downloadDisabled.jpg" /> means that you cannot download the datasets products.
				</para>
				<para>
					To select a dataset, the user has to scroll out the list and
					choose the dataset by clicking on the list entry. It is also
					possible to filter the available list of datasets by the means
					of the filter combo boxes. The filtering criteria are received
					from the server, but they should mainly contain : mission,
					sensor and keywords. 
					<graphic fileref="screenshots/datasetFilters.jpg" /> 
					<para>By default, all the
					criteria are set to "None". As soon as a criteria is chosen in
					one of the combo boxes, the datasets are filtered and the list is
					updated, taken into account the other combo boxes selected
					criteria.</para>
					<graphic fileref="screenshots/datasetFiltering1.jpg" /> 
						
					<para>Here is an examaple of the mission and sensor criteria set to S2 and OPT.</para>	
					<graphic fileref="screenshots/datasetFiltering2.jpg" />			
					<para>
					In order to disable the filtering for a criterion, set back the
					selected option to "None".</para>
				</para>
			</sect2>
			<sect2><title>Search Criteria</title>
				<para>
					Once a dataset has been selected, to set the search criteria,
					the user has to click on the button <inlinegraphic fileref="screenshots/toolBarIcons/searchIcon.jpg" /> on the left	toolbar.
					The search criteria widget is then displayed. <graphic fileref="screenshots/dateCriteria.jpg" />
					It is composed of several accordion, each accordion displays a search criteria type. Each button on the footer has his own role.</para>
		
				<para>The Search button submits the search request to the server to
				retrieve the results. See <xref linkend="resultsTable"/>.</para>
				<para>The Share button when	clicked, displays a popup. <inlinegraphic fileref="screenshots/sharePopup.jpg" />
				Clik on url, a new browser window is opened, the search widget is displayed with all the search parameters set.
				</para>
				<para>
					<inlinegraphic fileref="screenshots/tip.jpg" /><emphasis>The openSearch url to
						submit is created according to all the criteria selected inside
						the search criteria widget.</emphasis>
				</para> 
				<para>There search criteria types are :</para>
					<sect3><title>Date Criteria</title>
						<para>
							They consist in the start and stop dates of the selected
							dataset. In order to change the selected date, click on the
							icon <inlinegraphic fileref="screenshots/calendarTriggererButton.jpg" /> to
							display the calendar widget. 
							<graphic fileref="screenshots/calandarWidget.jpg" /> 
							Choose the month and year using the combo boxes, then click on the day date. The
							calendar widget is closed and the chosen date does appear in
							the text field.
						</para>
						<para>
							<inlinegraphic fileref="screenshots/tip.jpg" /> <emphasis>The same methods are used to modify both the start and stop dates.</emphasis>
						</para>
						<para>
							It is also possible to change the dates using a time slider. To enable the time slider, check the checkbox <inlinegraphic fileref="screenshots/timeSliderCheckBox.jpg" />.
							The search widget is then hidden and the timeSlider is displayed in the bottom of the map.
						</para>						
						<graphic fileref="screenshots/timeSlider.jpg" />
						<para>	Drag the time bar to move and change the time range. </para>
						<para>It is also possible to move the time slider bar by clicking on the left and right arrows of the time slider.
						The bar is then moved respectively to the left or to the right.</para>
						<graphic fileref="screenshots/timeSliderBar.jpg" />
						<para>
							Drag the bar left handle and the bar right handle to enlarge the time range or to make it smaller.
						</para>
						<para>
							<inlinegraphic fileref="screenshots/tip.jpg" /> <emphasis>Each time the bar is moved or resized, a search is launched and the results are displayed on the map.</emphasis>
						</para>
					</sect3>
					<sect3><title>Area Criteria</title>
						<para>
							They consist in geographical criteria to be used in the
							search. To visualize the area widget, click on Area tab inside
							the search criteria widget. 
						</para>	
						<graphic fileref="screenshots/areaWidget.jpg" />

						<para>The area is created using either a rectangular zone, a polygon a Gazetteer or can be imported from a file.</para>					
						
						<para><emphasis>A rectangle search area or a BBOX </emphasis>is defined by :
							<itemizedlist>
								<listitem><para>West: the maximum longitude</para></listitem>
								<listitem><para>East: the minimum longitude</para></listitem>
								<listitem><para>North: the maximum latitude</para></listitem>
								<listitem><para>South: the minimum latitude</para></listitem>
							</itemizedlist>
							By default, the coordinates are synchronized with the map
							extent. To disable this behavior uncheck the <inlinegraphic fileref="screenshots/useExtentCheckBox.jpg" /> check box. 
							Thus the coordinates can be entered manually is each text field.
						</para>
						
						<para>
							<para><emphasis>A Polygon search area </emphasis> is defined by its coordinates.</para>
						
							<para>To enable drawing polygons, click on the Polygon button <inlinegraphic
							fileref="screenshots/polygonButton.jpg" />in the area widget.
							The polygon definition view is displayed.
							</para> 
							<graphic fileref="screenshots/polygonWidget.jpg" /> 
							<para>Enter the polygon coordinates in the text field under 'Enter coordinates:' and then press the Draw button
							<inlinegraphic fileref="screenshots/drawButton.jpg" />.
							</para>
							<para>The polygon is then drawn on the map.</para>
							<graphic fileref="screenshots/drawnPolygon.jpg" />
							
							<para>It is also possible to draw a polygon using the mouse.
							On the polygon view, press the Draw button <inlinegraphic fileref="screenshots/drawButton.jpg" />, then click on the map to select a polygon edge.
							Move the mouse to choose another point an so on. When all the points are choosen double click to finish the definition of the polygon.
							The polygon widget is then displayed with the polygon coordinates.
							</para>
							<para>
							<inlinegraphic fileref="screenshots/tip.jpg" /> <emphasis>To remove a polygon, select its coordinates in the text field, delete them an then press the Draw button.</emphasis>
							</para>
						</para>	
						
						<para>
							<para><emphasis>A Gazetteer search area</emphasis> can be defined by clicking on the <inlinegraphic
							fileref="screenshots/gazetteerButton.jpg" /> in the area widget.
							The gazetteer view is displayed.</para>
							
							<graphic fileref="screenshots/gazetteerWidget.jpg" /> 
							<para>Enter the location to search in the text field and the press the Enter keyboard.</para>
							<para>The location items retrieved from the server are displayed in a list.</para>
							<graphic fileref="screenshots/gazetteerResult.jpg" />
							<para>Click on the choosen location to define the search area.</para>
						</para>
						
						<para><emphasis>To import a search Area</emphasis> click on the <inlinegraphic fileref="screenshots/importButton.jpg" /> in the area widget.
							The import view is displayed.
						</para>
						<graphic fileref="screenshots/importWidget.jpg" /> 
						<para>Drag a KML, GML or GeoJSON file from the file system and then drop it in the Drop zone of the import view.</para>
						<para>The imported zone in the drawn on the map and a notification message appears underneath the Drop zone.</para>
						<para>
							<inlinegraphic fileref="screenshots/warning.jpg" /> <emphasis>Only KML, GML and GeoJSON files can be imported.</emphasis>
						</para>
				</sect3>
					
				<sect3><title>Advanced Criteria</title>
						<para>They are criteria relative to the selected dataset, so
							they change depending on the dataset chosen.
						<para>
							<inlinegraphic fileref="screenshots/tip.jpg" /> <emphasis>Different datasets
								can have the same criteria. It is a configuration matter on
								the server side.</emphasis>
						</para> To visualize the advanced criteria, click on Advanced Criteria
						tab inside the search criteria widget. <graphic
						fileref="screenshots/advancedCriteria.jpg" /> Each criterion is
						displayed by its name and a selection widget. Criteria having a
						range are displayed with sliders. Move the slider or set the
						value inside the text field to change the selected value.
						Criteria having a multiple selection possibilities are
						displayed with a list of checkboxes. Check or uncheck the check
						boxes to change the criterion selected value.
						</para>
						<para>
							<inlinegraphic fileref="screenshots/warning.jpg" /> <emphasis>If no dataset
								has been selected and the Advanced Criteria tab is selected a
								notification message is displayed to the user and no criteria
								is displayed.</emphasis>
						</para>
				</sect3>
				
				<sect3><title>Download Options</title>
						<para>They are options relative to the selected dataset, so
							they change depending on the dataset chosen.
						<para>
							<inlinegraphic fileref="screenshots/tip.jpg" /> <emphasis>Different datasets
								can have the same download options. It is a configuration
								matter on the server side.</emphasis>
						</para> To visualize the download options, click on the Download
						Options tab inside the search criteria widget.
						<graphic fileref="screenshots/downloadOptions.jpg" />

						Each option is displayed by its name and a combobox containing
						the possible values.
						</para>
						<para>
							<inlinegraphic fileref="screenshots/warning.jpg" /> <emphasis>If no dataset
								has been selected and the Download Options tab is selected a
								notification message is displayed to the user and no download
								option is displayed.</emphasis>
						</para>
				</sect3>				
			</sect2>
			</sect1>
			
			<sect1><title>Search Results</title>
					<sect2><title id="resultsTable">Table Results</title>
						<para>
							Once the search criteria have been filled in and the Search button clicked,
							results are availabe in a table with the products metadata	in the bottom of the home page.
							Click on the table button <inlinegraphic fileref="screenshots/tableButton.jpg" />  to display the results table.
						</para>
							<graphic fileref="screenshots/resultsTable.jpg" />
						<para>
							<inlinegraphic fileref="screenshots/warning.jpg" /> <emphasis>If no dataset has
								been selected and the <inlinegraphic fileref="screenshots/tableButton.jpg" /> is clicked,
								the results table is empty.
							</emphasis>
						</para>
						<para>
							<inlinegraphic fileref="screenshots/tip.jpg" /> <emphasis>The results table can
								be hidden by clicking on the <inlinegraphic
								fileref="screenshots/tableButton.jpg" /> button on
								the toolbar.
							</emphasis>
						</para>
						<para>
							The navigation in the table results is insured by the buttons in the middle of the status bar <inlinegraphic fileref="screenshots/tablePaginationButtons.jpg" />.
							The "First" button displays the first page of the results.
							The "Last" button displays the last page of the results.
							The "Previous" and "Next" buttons allow the navigation from one page to the previous or the next one.
						</para>
						
						<para>
							The field <inlinegraphic fileref="screenshots/resultsSearchFilter.jpg" />
							allows to filter the results according to the text entred.
						</para>
					</sect2>
					<sect2><title id="directDownload">Direct Download</title>
						<para>
							The Direct Download is a functionnality of the user client
							making the user download the retrieved products if they have a
							url starting with <emphasis>http or https</emphasis>. In the results table,
							<emphasis>downloadable products are highlighted by an underlined product
							identifier.</emphasis> 
						</para>
						<graphic fileref="screenshots/downloadableProduct.jpg"	alt='DOWNLOADABLE PRODUCT IMAGE' />
						<para>
							For a <emphasis>downloadable product</emphasis>, click on the product id. The direct
							download widget is opened. 
						</para>
						<graphic fileref="screenshots/directDownloadWidget.jpg"
								alt='DIRECT DOWNLOAD WIDGET IMAGE' />
						<para>According to the product url and to the download managers
							registered, the user can have the choice to either choose a
							download via:
						<itemizedlist>
							<listitem><para>the browser</para></listitem>
							<listitem><para>or the local download manager</para></listitem>
						</itemizedlist>
						</para>
					</sect2>
					
					<sect2><title id="simpleDar">Data Access Request</title>

						<para>A Data Access Request is a request to the server
							issued from the results table with product items having a url field filled in. </para>
						
						<para>This request aims to issue a download request for all the items
							included when they will be downloadable. A download manager has
							to be assigned to the request and will insure the download.</para>

						<para>To include products in a Simple Data Access Request, check
							the products checkboxes in the results table.</para>
						<para>
							<inlinegraphic fileref="screenshots/tip.jpg" /> <emphasis>If the Retrieve
								Product button <inlinegraphic fileref="screenshots/retrieveProductButton.jpg"
								alt='RETRIEVE PRODUCT BUTTON' /> is still disabled this means
								that the products selected does not have a url. So change the
								selected products.
							</emphasis>
						</para>

						<para>
							Click on Retrieve Product button to display the data access
							widget with the list of available download managers. <graphic
								fileref="screenshots/darWidget.jpg" />
						</para>

						<para>The "Validate" button makes the validation
							request sent to the server, and the server response displayed
							underneath the button. If the request is successfully validated,
							the estimated size of the products are displayed and a
							notification message confirms that the request has been
							acknowleged. The Validation button is renamed into "Confirm":</para>
							<graphic
								fileref="screenshots/validatedDARWidget.jpg" />
						<para>
							<inlinegraphic fileref="screenshots/tip.jpg" /> <emphasis>If the validation has
								failed an error message is dispalyed.</emphasis>
						</para>

						<para>
							Click on "Confirm" button to submit, the confirmation
							request to the server. The server response is displayed
							underneath the button. If the request has been successfully
							confirmed, the request is being processed, unless an error
							message is dispalyed. 
						</para>
						<para>
							The close icon <inlinegraphic fileref="screenshots/widgetCloseIcon.jpg" /> aims to close the widget.
						</para>
					</sect2>

					<sect2><title id="STODar">Standing Order Data Access Request</title>
						<para>A Standing Order Data Access Request allows the user to schedule a search either by time or data criteria
						in order to retrieve and download products. Thus, a download manager has
							to be assigned to the request and will insure the download.</para>
											
						<para>This functionnality is available from the Subscribe button <inlinegraphic fileref="screenshots/toolBarIcons/subscribeButton.jpg" /> in the left toolbar.</para>
						<graphic fileref="screenshots/subscribeWidget.jpg" />
						<para>The "Data-driven Order" radio button is selected by default to submit a <emphasis>data-driven</emphasis> Standing Order</para>
						
						<para>Fill in the fields (same as a search) and click on the Order button. Then the list of available download managers is displayed.
						<graphic
								fileref="screenshots/darWidget.jpg" />
						</para>
						
						<para>The "Validate" button makes the validation
							request sent to the server, and the server response is displayed
							underneath the button. If the request is successfully validated, a
							notification message confirms that the request has been
							acknowleged. The validation button is renamed into "Confirm" <graphic
								fileref="screenshots/validatedDARWidget.jpg" /></para>
						<para>
							<inlinegraphic fileref="screenshots/tip.jpg" /> <emphasis>If the validation has
								failed an error message is dispalyed.</emphasis>
						</para>

						<para>
							Click on "Confirm" button to submit, the confirmation
							request to the server. The server response is displayed
							underneath the button. If the request has been successfully
							confirmed, the request is being processed, unless an error
							message is dispalyed. 
						</para>
						<para>
							The close icon <inlinegraphic fileref="screenshots/widgetCloseIcon.jpg"
								alt='WIDGET CLOSE ICON' /> aims to close the widget.
						</para>
						
						<para> To submit a <emphasis>time-driven </emphasis> standing order click on the Time Driven radio button
						<inlinegraphic fileref="screenshots/timeSTORadio.jpg" /> and fill in the additionnal time-driven scheduling options and follow the same steps than the <emphasis>data-Driven</emphasis> Standing Order.
						<graphic fileref="screenshots/timeSTOWidget.jpg" /></para>
								
						<para><emphasis>Time-Driven and Data-Driven requests can be shared by clicking on the Share button of the widget.
						a popup will appear with the url to share. Copy the url and paste it in a new window. The Standing order widget is opened with the 
						same criteria.</emphasis>
						</para>
					</sect2>
					<sect2><title>Hosted Processing</title>
						<para>A processing can be added when a product is downloaded through a Data Access Request.</para>
						<para>The different processing available are accessible when a Data Access Request is created by opening the Processing accordion.</para>
						<graphic fileref="screenshots/darProcessingWidget.jpg" />
						<para>Click on a listed processing to select it for the Data Acccess Request.</para>
						<graphic fileref="screenshots/processingSelection.jpg" />
						<para>Then, click on Configure to set the processing parameters. Parameters are specific for each processing.</para>
					</sect2>
			</sect1>
			
			<sect1 id="shopcart"><title>Shopcart</title>
					<para>The user has a current shopcart available in the Data Access Services area. He can manage its shopcarts in My Account area. See <xref linkend="shopcartMgmt"/>
					</para>

				<sect2>
					<title>Content</title>
					<para>The current shopcart content is displayed directly in the map.</para>
					<para>Click on Shopcart button <inlinegraphic fileref="screenshots/shopcartButton.jpg" /> to display the name of the current shopcart being used.</para>
					<para>Click on Table button <inlinegraphic fileref="screenshots/shopcartTableButton.jpg" /> to display the items in a table.</para>
					<graphic fileref="screenshots/shopcartTable.jpg" />
				</sect2>
				<sect2>
					<title>Manage shopcart items</title>
						Items are added into the current shopcart via :
						<itemizedlist>
							<listitem><para>Map : click on a product in the map and then click on Add To Shopcart button<graphic fileref="screenshots/mapPopupAddShopcart.jpg" /></para></listitem>
							<listitem><para>Table : select products and then click on Add to Shopcart button <inlinegraphic fileref="screenshots/addShopcartButton.jpg" /></para></listitem>
						</itemizedlist>
						
						In the Shopcart table, the user can :
						<itemizedlist>
							<listitem><para>Update the download options of the selected shopcart items.</para></listitem>
							<listitem><para>Delete the selected items from the shopcart</para></listitem>
							<listitem><para>Export the selected items in KML, Atom or HTML format</para></listitem>
						</itemizedlist>
				</sect2>
			</sect1>
			
			<sect1><title id="map">Map</title>
				<sect2>
					<title id="mapModes">Map Modes</title> 
						ngEO user interface offers to the user two map modes 2D and 3D. Both modes are used to :
						<itemizedlist>
							<listitem><para>- vizualize the products footprints</para></listitem>
							<listitem><para>- navigate on the globe</para></listitem>
							<listitem><para>- choose search area coordinates</para></listitem>
		<!-- 					<listitem><para>draw search area</para></listitem> -->
							<listitem><para>- project product browse images</para></listitem>
							<listitem><para>- vizualize map layers</para></listitem>
							<listitem><para>- choose map background</para></listitem>
						
						</itemizedlist>
						These functionnalities are detailed in the next sections.
						
						<para>Click on the 2D/3D <inlinegraphic fileref="screenshots/toolBarIcons/mapMode.jpg"/> button on the toolbar to change the map mode
						from 2D to 3D and inversely.</para>
				</sect2>

				<sect2><title id="navigation">Navigation</title> 
						<para> In order to zoom in either:
							<itemizedlist>
								<listitem><para>- Click on the Zooum In <inlinegraphic fileref="screenshots/toolBarIcons/zoomInIcon.jpg"/>button on the toolbar</para></listitem>
								<listitem><para>- or move the mouse wheel in.</para></listitem>
							</itemizedlist>
						</para>

						<para> In order to zoom out either:
							<itemizedlist>
								<listitem><para>- Click on the Zooum Out <inlinegraphic fileref="screenshots/toolBarIcons/zoomOutIcon.jpg"/>button on the toolbar to zoom out. </para></listitem>
								<listitem><para>- or move the mouse wheel out.</para></listitem>
							</itemizedlist>
						</para>
						<para>Click on the Start View <inlinegraphic fileref="screenshots/toolBarIcons/startViewIcon.jpg"/>button on the toolbar to return back to the initial view.</para>
				</sect2>

				<sect2><title id="productsOnMap">Products on Map</title> 
						<para>Once a catalogue search in done and the products are retrieved, the related footprints are drawn on the map.
						</para>
						
						<para>Click inside a footprint:
							<itemizedlist>
								<listitem><para>- the browse image is projected on the footprint,</para></listitem>
								<listitem><para>- the product row is checked on the results table</para></listitem>
								<listitem><para>- a popup widget is displayed with information on the selected product</para></listitem>
								<listitem><para>- the icon <inlinegraphic fileref="screenshots/darIcon.jpg" alt='SIMPLE DAR icon'/> allows submitting a Simple Data access Request.
								Follow the same steps as in section <xref linkend="simpleDARHowTo"/>
								</para></listitem> 							
								<inlinegraphic fileref="screenshots/itemOnMap.jpg" alt='ITEM ON MAP'/>
							</itemizedlist>
						</para>
				</sect2>

				<sect2><title id="layers">Map Layers</title> 
						<para>To access the map layers, click on the layers icon on the toolbar <inlinegraphic fileref="screenshots/toolBarIcons/layersIcon.jpg" alt='LAYERS ICON'/>.</para>
						<para>The layers widget is displayed.</para>
						 <graphic fileref="screenshots/layersWidget.jpg" alt='LAYERS WIDGET'/>
						<para>The Results Footprints layers is checked by default. It is the layer which displayed the result items footprints on the map.
						</para>
						<para>Check the checkbox in front of the layer name, the layer is mapped on the map.</para> 
							<graphic fileref="screenshots/projectedLayers.jpg" alt='PROJECTED LAYERS'/>
						<para>In order to remove a layer from the map, uncheck the checkbox in front of the layer name.</para>

				</sect2>

				<sect2><title id="backgroudS">Map Background</title> 
						<para>To access the available map backgrouds, click on the background icon on the toolbar <inlinegraphic fileref="screenshots/toolBarIcons/backgroundIcon.jpg" alt='BACKGROUND ICON'/>.</para>
						<para>The backgrounds' widget is displayed.</para>
						<graphic fileref="screenshots/backgroundsWidget.jpg" alt='BACKGROUND WIDGET'/>
						<para>Click, then, on the radio button in front of the background name to change the map background.</para>
				</sect2>
			</sect1>

	</chapter>
	
	<chapter id="account">
		<title>My Account Services</title>

		<sect1 id="downloadManagers"><title>Download Managers Monitoring</title>

			<para>The "Download Managers" tab in My account menu is dedicated to
				monitor the users'download managers. Several download managers can
				be installed by a user on different working machines. The user
				interface allows to install a local download manager through the
				three buttons displayed in the Download managers tab. Each button is related to an OS specific download manager installer: Windows, Linux and MasOS.</para>

			<para>The view is accessible through My account entry on the menu
				bar.
			<para>
				Information details are displayed for each of the available
				download managers : status, identifier, name, user ID, IP Address
				and the last access date. <graphic
					fileref="screenshots/downloadManagersView.jpg"
					alt='DOWNLOAD MANAGERS' />
			</para>
			</para>

			<para>A registered download manager can have one of the three
				possible statuses:
			<itemizedlist>
				<listitem><para>ACTIVE: is represented by the <inlinegraphic
					fileref="screenshots/activeIcon.jpg" alt='MENUBAR IMAGE' /> icon. An
					ACTIVE download manager is actually downloading products.
				</para></listitem>

				<listitem><para>INACTIVE: is represented by the <inlinegraphic
					fileref="screenshots/inactiveIcon.jpg" alt='MENUBAR IMAGE' /> icon.
					An INACTIVE download manager is an available download manager but
					does not have ongoing downloading tasks.
				</para></listitem>

				<listitem><para>STOPPED: is represented by the <inlinegraphic
					fileref="screenshots/cancelledIcon.jpg" alt='MENUBAR IMAGE' /> icon.
					A STOPPED download manager is a download manager which has been
					stopped and so it is not working.
				</para></listitem>
			</itemizedlist>
			</para>

			<para>A registered download manager can be managed once it is
				selected with the commands:
			<itemizedlist>
				<listitem><para>Stop: is represented by the button <inlinegraphic
					fileref="screenshots/dmStopButton.jpg" alt='STOP DM BUTTON' />.
					<para>This command makes the download manager stop be assigned to product downloads, 
					purge scheduled/paused Product downloads, but continue ongoing downloading activities until these are finished.</para>
				</para></listitem>

				<listitem><para>Stop Immediately: is represented respectively by the
					button <inlinegraphic fileref="screenshots/dmStopImmediatelyButton.jpg"
					alt='STOP DM BUTTON' /> icon.
					<para>This command makes the download manager stop be assigned to product downloads and stop all ongoing and scheduled/paused Product downloads.</para>
				</para></listitem>
			</itemizedlist>
			<para>
				To manage a download manager, click on its row in the table, the
				command buttons are updated according to the download manager
				status. When a command button is clicked, the status change
				request is sent to the server and a notification message is
				displayed. <graphic
					fileref="screenshots/downloadManagerCommands.jpg"
					alt='DOWNLOAD MANAGER MONITORING MESSAGE' />
			</para>

			<para>
				<inlinegraphic fileref="screenshots/warning.jpg" /> <emphasis>Only the ACTIVE and
					INACTIVE download managers can be managed.</emphasis> <emphasis>STOPPED
					download managers are only displayed.</emphasis>

			</para>
			<para>
				<inlinegraphic fileref="screenshots/warning.jpg" /> <emphasis>Once the Stop or the
					Stop Immediately buttons are clicked, a new command cannot be
					issued from the user interface. A notification message is
					displayed to notify the user.</emphasis> <graphic
					fileref="screenshots/dmMonitoringMessage.jpg"
					alt='DOWNLOAD MANAGER MONITORING MESSAGE' />
			</para>
			</para>
			
		</sect1>


		<sect1 id="dars"><title>Data Access Requests Monitoring</title> User's
			submitted data access requests can be viewed and monitored through
			the Data Access Requests tab accessible through My account entry on
			the menu bar. <graphic
			fileref="screenshots/darsView.jpg" alt='DARS VIEW' />
			<para>On the left side, the download managers already assigned to
				data access requests are displayed. On the right side is displayed
				the list of the users' data access requests.</para>
			
			<para><emphasis>Data Access Requests are either Simple Data Access Requests or Standing Order Data Access Requests.</emphasis></para>

			<para>
				The request list can be filtered by the download manager they are
				assigned to. By clicking, on the download manager name, the
				requests list is updated. <graphic
					fileref="screenshots/darsFiltering.jpg" alt='DARS FILTERING' />
			</para>

			<para>
				<inlinegraphic fileref="screenshots/tip.jpg" /> <emphasis>Click on the highlighted
					download manager name to disable the filtering.</emphasis> 
					<graphic fileref="screenshots/dmMonitoringMessage.jpg" alt='DOWNLOAD MANAGER MONITORING MESSAGE' />
			</para>
			
			
			<para>A data access request can have one of the the possible statuses:
				<itemizedlist>
					<listitem><para>Processing: is an going request, it is represented by the <inlinegraphic
						fileref="screenshots/activeIcon.jpg" alt='MENUBAR IMAGE' /> icon.
					</para></listitem>

					<listitem><para>Paused: is paused request, it is represented by the <inlinegraphic
						fileref="screenshots/inactiveIcon.jpg" alt='MENUBAR IMAGE' /> icon.
					</para></listitem>

					<listitem><para>Cancelled: is a cancelled request, it is represented by the <inlinegraphic
						fileref="screenshots/cancelledIcon.jpg" alt='MENUBAR IMAGE' /> icon.
					</para></listitem>
					
					<listitem><para>Completed: is a completed request. 
<!-- 						it is represented by the <inlinegraphic fileref="screenshots/cancelledIcon.jpg" alt='MENUBAR IMAGE' /> icon. -->
					</para></listitem>
				</itemizedlist>
			</para>			
			
			<para>Each request has details information. In order to seen them, click on the a data access request to expand its content. <inlinegraphic
				fileref="screenshots/expandedDAR.jpg" alt='EXPANDED DAR' />.
				<para>The data access request id, status, completion percentage
					and the number of products are displayed.</para>
				<para>Buttons Pause, Resume and Stop Immediately buttons are
					displayed according to the request status.</para>
			</para>
			<para>Each Simple Data Access Request has products when it is submitted.
				However, standing order requests are submitted with scheduling options, so they do not have product urls when they are created.
				<para>During standing order request processing, when the products are ready, they should should appears in the Products sections. </para>
				
				<para>Click on the Products button to visualize the products details.</para>
				<graphic fileref="screenshots/expandedDARProducts.jpg"
							alt='EXPANDED DAR PRODUCTS' />
			</para>
			<itemizedlist>
				<listitem><para><para>
						Click on the Stop definitively button <inlinegraphic
							fileref="screenshots/stopDefinitivelyButton.jpg"
							alt='DOWNLOAD MANAGER STOP DEFINITIVELY BUTTON' /> to cancel a
						processing or a paused data access request.
					</para></para></listitem>
				<listitem><para><para>
						Click on the Pause button <inlinegraphic fileref="screenshots/pauseButton.jpg"
							alt='PAUSE BUTTON' /> to pause a processing data access request.
					</para></para></listitem>
				<listitem><para><para>
						Click on the Resume button <inlinegraphic fileref="screenshots/resumeButton.jpg"
							alt='RESUME BUTTON' /> to change the status of a paused data
						access request to processing.
					</para></para></listitem>
			</itemizedlist>
		</sect1>
		<sect1 id="prefs"><title>User Preferences</title>
			<para>
				Click on the User Preferences tab in My account, the view lists just the last selected dataset and background layer.
				
			</para>
			<graphic
					fileref="screenshots/prefsTab.jpg" alt='Prefs Tab' />
			<para> To reset the preferences, click on the Reset Preferences button <inlinegraphic 
					fileref="screenshots/resetPrefsButton.jpg" alt='Prefs button' />.</para>
			<para>
				<inlinegraphic fileref="screenshots/warning.jpg" /> <emphasis>The preferences storage is not cross-browsers compatible. They are only reloaded when using the same browser new window. </emphasis>
			</para>
					
		</sect1>
		
		<sect1 id="shopcartMgmt"><title>Shopcarts Management</title>
			<para>
				Click on the Shopcarts tab in My account, the view all the available shopcarts from the user.				
			</para>
			<graphic fileref="screenshots/shopcartsTab.jpg" />
			<para>Click on shopcart to change the current shopcart accessible in the Data Access Services area.</para>
			<para>The following actions are avaible in the buttons below : </para>
			<itemizedlist>
				<listitem><para>Click on New to create a new empty shopcart.</para></listitem>
				<listitem><para>Click on Share to share your shopcart.</para></listitem>
				<listitem><para>Click on Export to export the shopcart content in KML, Atom or HTML format.</para></listitem>
				<listitem><para>Click on Rename to rename the current shopcart.</para></listitem>
				<listitem><para>Click on Duplicate to duplicate all the current shopcart content in a new shopcart.</para></listitem>
				<listitem><para>Click on Delete to remove the curernt shopcart.</para></listitem>
			</itemizedlist>
		</sect1>
		
		<sect1 id="inquiries"><title>Inquiries</title>
			<para>
				Click on the Inquiries tab in My account, the view displays the inquiry form.
				
			</para>
			<graphic fileref="screenshots/inquiriesTab.jpg" />
			<para>To choose the inquiry type, click on the combobox and choose one of the possible inquiry types:
			Suggestion, Question, Complaint, Request for bulk order, Request on-demand media delivery, Other.</para>
			<para> The inquiry text message has to be typed in the text area underneath</para>
			Finally click on the Submit button <inlinegraphic fileref="screenshots/inquiriesSubmitButton.jpg" alt='Prefs Tab' />to submit the inquiry request.
		</sect1>

	</chapter>
	
	
</book>
